Guide to the Pumping Plant for Lawrence Water Company Collection
University of Kansas
Original plans for Pumping Plant for Lawrence Water Company
1913
University of Kansas Kenneth Spencer Research Library Kansas Collection 1450 Poplar Lane, Lawrence, KS 66045-7616 Phone: (785)864-4334 Fax: (785)864-5803 URL: http://spencer.lib.ku.edu
1 oversized folder (90 cm. x 120 cm.)
This collection is comprised of 8 original drawings for the pumping plant at the Lawrence Water Company. The plans were made official by the City Engineer at the time E.H. Dunmire.
RH MS S29
Organizations:
Lawrence (Kan.) Water Dept.
Subjects:
Pumping stations--Kansas--Lawrence--Designs and plans.
Names:
Dunmire, Elijah Herbert.
Restrictions on Access
None
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
- RH MS S29
  - Drawing No.
    - Floor Plans: first and second floors, 1913 July 17 (Folder 1)
    - Cross Sections: AA and BB, [1913 July --] (Folder 2)
    - Cross Section CC, 1913 July 19 (Folder 3)
    - West Side Elevation, [1913 July --] (Folder 4)
    - South Side Elevation, 1913 July 25 (Folder 5)
    - East Side Elevation, 1913 July 25 (Folder 6)
    - Cross Section East and West through pump station, [1913 July --] (Drawing not numbered)
    - Plan and West elevation of stand tower, 1913 July 26 (Drawing not numbered)